As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go Get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are
in between the sea and
the sky Ready now for adventure We're itching
to try Get ready to roam So all aboard
now we're set to go Set sail to the ocean
so deep Ready for a truly grand adventure
Well don't you think that sounds really
fun All this excitement is second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mass.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
I've had enough ghosts for today?
I don't need a whole island of them.
Wait a sec.
What about that ghost we saw before, huh?
Is it still here on the boat? No,
looked like it was
flying to the island I'm
guessing that's where the
thing came from Interesting
Like Brooke said,
the lab noise we heard earlier Was
from that gate over there closing shut
So it's not that we ran into it
But that we were eaten by the mouth
it ate us the fog makes it
difficult to tell but i imagine
that the walls we see here
extend all the way around the
island in a circle that means
that we were intentionally
pulled in and now that the gate
is closed we're trapped inside
i see that's why the skeleton
told us to run away it's
because we're stuck inside some
kind of trap wait then that
would mean the people here are
capturing sailors on purpose
right but why if this is a
moving island that means we're
still technically out at sea
guess it won't be able to
anchor down here hold on that's
the last thing we want to do
we gotta get out of this place
right now bad news you guys
i think i have i can't go on
that island sickness me too i'm
real sick no problem you two
watch the ship and you've got
stupid adventure sickness again
come to your senses come on
look at that that creepy
looking building is a Bone Fight
haunted mansion if i've ever seen
one and i'm not talking about
the fun kind either the kind
will you never make it out
alive you worry too much i'm
not going there to pick a fight
i promise i'll be careful i
just want to catch that ghost
and keep it as a pet you're
gonna get us all killed either
way brook's a part of our crew
now so i have to bring him
back saji give me pirate lunchbox
he's a part of our crew hey
i did not vote for that if we
have a living skeleton wandering
around the ship i won't be
able to sleep at night here
i've got the lunch boxes
luffy Franky it's up to you to
take care of robin while i watch
the boat nothing gets my cola
pumping like an adventure on
a crazy new island robin you
aren't seriously going with them
are you it does sound exciting
right now listen up obviously
we're going to use a smaller
boat to pull us close to the
shore and the soldier dock
system has something pretty
damn super for that i've been
keeping this one a surprise it's
channel two what's that good
question.
The system has six channels.
Two of them are zero.
Then there's one, two, three, and four.
Naturally, each dock has
its own set of capabilities.
We know the zeros are for paddling, and
we've already seen one and three, but...
Didn't you tell us a while back that docks
two and four were empty?
I just told you that so I
could surprise you later.
Soldier dock system
channel 2, launch! Ooh!
I can't wait to see what it is!
A battleship shopping boat!
Not bad, huh?
I call it Mini Mary 2!
It's really Mary!
Our Mary's been reborn as a landing crab!
She may be tiny, but I'm
happy to ride her again.
Now this is one surprise that
was definitely worth the wait.
Thanks, Franky. I love it.
With a ship like that, I can go shopping
for food in style anytime I want.
Hurry up and let me ride it.
Gotta say, that was
pretty thoughtful of you.
Hold your horses, pal.
We'll have our chance to take
her for a ride soon enough.
For now, how about we let
those three have a little fun?
So is that all the doc
stuff, or what? Uh-huh.
Including Channel 1 and 3 that I showed
you before, now you've seen it all.
Channel 0, support paddle.
Channel 1, a single-seat
waver, the white hobby horse.
Channel 3, a triple-seater scouting
submarine, the shark-submerged 3.
And then, Channel 2, a four-person
shopping boat, the mini-Mary 2.
For now, at least, those are all the
features of the ship's soldier dock system.
If you think of the
Sunny as our mothership?
Then these guys are all
the little soldiers.
that help her out.
Yeah, I love it!
You're a genius, Franky!
Keep it up! Good boy!
Good, good, good, good!
Hell yeah!
What can I say?
I guess I'm extra awesome this week, huh?
Silver!
Nami?
Nami! What's wrong?
You're not in trouble, are you?
Hmm can't see a damn thing out there.
It's just fog and more fog
It sounded like it came from the island.
No fair!
You gotta come back so I
can ride the mini Mary, too.
That's all you're worried about.
What about Nami chopper
a new supper out there,
too You know just saying
I Wonder perhaps they
fell victim to a curse
from that ghost come on.
That's not funny
What was that? Crazy!
The anchor just dropped on its own!
I just built it, so there's no
way that the gears got loose.
Well, either way, pull it up.
We can't have the ship
lose its balance now.
That's weird.
Did somebody touch the hatch?
Hey, now is not the time for this crap.
Could you take things seriously for once?
Wait, it's not me.
I swear I'm not doing this.
Look out!
You nuts!
What are you trying to pull here?
No, I just moved on its own.
This is strange I got a
hunch we're not alone here.
Then there's an enemy on this ship so
you think it's a ghost doing this stuff?
Or is it someone with
a Devil Fruit power who
or whatever it is at least
we know they're close.
Just now I heard what sounded like
some sort of beast growling a beast.
Right now.
I'm more concerned about Nami.
You guys take care of the boat.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna swim over to the
island and rescue her of course.
Whoa, that was lame!
He can't can he?
Hey, you, uh, having problems?
Shut up, damn it!
You saw what happened to me!
Whatever it is, it wants
to keep us on the ship.
We can't see this bastard at all.
It could take us out one by one, and
we couldn't do a damn thing about it.
What's going on, Robin?
Something is grabbing me.
You bastard, get your
invisible hands off her!
It really does sound
like some kind of animal.
What is it now?
Look, I don't know what's going on,
but we got waves inside the wall.
They're pushing us away from the island.
I got you. You okay? I think so.
It seems to be gone.
Quick, raise the anchor.
If you think you can do it without
falling on your face again.
At least I'm not throwing swords!
Usopp! Chopper! Say something!
Crap!
We're gonna get separated from them!
Hey, Franky!
You gotta have some kind of secret
weapon for a time like this!
Alright!
I'll bust out the surprise hat!
Yee!
Sounds like blood!
Wait, no!
That was quite the fall.
That wall must be six
or seven meters high.
We're lucky we're still okay.
What is this place?
It's that ghost island, of course.
Ghost?
What?
So not like you're surprised.
We've already been over this, haven't we?
But if we were up there,
how did we get down here?
We got excited about the Mini Mary, and
before we knew it, we hit the shore.
We didn't notice it, but the wall
up there is the edge of the island.
When we ran into it, we were
all thrown off the boat.
Then we landed in this moat here.
Now, I admit that was 100 % my fault, but
I'm cute, so you'll forgive me, right?
Yeah, right after I smack you! Anyway,
what I don't get is why
they have a moat on the
other side of the wall
right at the entrance.
What's the point?
From the looks of things,
it's some kind of trap.
If you think of it that way,
we're lucky we didn't fall on
any spears or giant spikes.
You're right.
It's a good thing we had all these
skeletons here to cushion our fall, huh?
Uh-huh.
Would you stop that already?
Hey, but we're still
near the entrance, right?
If we stay put for a while,
Luffy will come and find us.
He might try, but we're below sea level.
Doesn't that put us in a bad spot?
Good point.
If we stay here, then
they might not notice us.
In that case?
We should find a way out of this
pit and wait for them by the shore.
I guess so, but which way should we go?
It all looks bad
What the heck is that thing a dog?
That's no dog. Huh?
Then what is it?
Oh no!
It can't be!
Cerberus.
Wait, what the heck's a
Cerberus? You don't know!
It's the guardian of the underworld.
Come on, there's no way that's real!
Look at it, you got a better explanation?
So did we die and go
to the underworld? No!
Don't even say that!
If we stop and lead us, keep running!
Did you notice something, Chopper?
What is it? A bike.
Hey, I'm on to you.
One of your heads is a
buck's head, isn't it?
I liked it better when it was yelping.
See, it is sensitive.
Look, I see stairs.
Now we can get up to the shore.
You're safe!
For a dog, it's sense
of smell sure is bad.
It's gone.
But what now?
It chased us all the way
into this creepy forest.
That monster is still
roaming around down there.
If we climb to the ground and wait
for help, it could find us again.
Quite the quandary, isn't it?
For you!
Pardon my manners.
The name's Hildon.
Oh, and speaking of bad manners,
I was spying on all of you.
That dog really seemed to scare you.
The night has just begun, but already
the shadows in the forest are deep.
Soon it shall be transformed into a world
of terror far beyond
your worst nightmares.
Might I recommend you
take a ride with me in my
carriage we could go to the
mansion together mansion?
Of course.
Dr.
Hawkback's abode is just out the
way Huh what do you know i'm chopper
hey
i
didn't
get a good look at them so
maybe it's my imagination
But don't those horses seem a
bit strange it's dark your
eyes are playing tricks on you
Well if you say so i'm sure it's fine anyway
thanks for saving us back there We were
in bad shape before you showed up it was
nothing have a drink to calm your nerves
Now this forest is filled with frightening
creatures it's dangerous
to pass through on foot
I was surprised i thought
cerberus was just a legend
but there it was three heads
gnashing and everything.
That thing must have
been some kind of mutant.
It just wasn't natural.
We were lucky we got up in that tree,
but I was afraid I'd never come
down again with that thing around.
If you're hoping to wait for your
friends, the mansion's the safest place.
Besides, they couldn't possibly miss it.
Not only that, we're gonna get to meet Dr.
Hog back too, right?
Is this Hog guy really that famous?
Are you kidding?
Every doctor in the world knows his name.
He's one of the greatest surgeons ever.
He can perform real miracles.
They say his operations have saved
more people than there are Stars in the
sky he has fame and fortune and every
other honor a doctor could ever hope for.
The entire medical community
looks up to him as a true hero.
But then he just
disappeared without a trace.
Some people thought he had an accident
and others thought that he was kidnapped.
But in the end since no one could find
any clues everyone gave up looking for
him and bit by bit we started thinking
of him as nothing more than a legend.
That is the hot fact you're
talking about, right?
Yes, indeed.
He's studying in seclusion.
The doctor came to this island to conduct
research beyond the scope of mankind.
Do you think I could get
an autograph from him?
I'm sure he could be persuaded to
spare a moment for one of his fans.
No way.
This island has lions, too?
What's wrong with you?
Don't scare me like that!
Come on!
What happened?
There was a lion but he...
His face was it looked like this...
Oh yeah right!
Want to see then?
Take a look for yourself!
Here
That is not right!
That is definitely not right!
Please, stop the carriage!
We need to turn around, Hildon!
My goodness, whatever could
have upset you so much?
Perhaps you all saw an illusion.
What do you mean illusion?
There was definitely
something out there for sure!
This forest is freaking strange!
That much is true.
It is a bit odd here.
The fog, for example,
has strange qualities.
It can even cause hallucinations for some.
So you mean it was just the fog?
Ah, that's good.
Illusion? The fog?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
Listen, Hildon, I'm sorry,
but we really do need you to take
us back to the coast right away.
Even if it's dangerous, the
three of us can manage somehow.
But I want to meet Dr. Hog back.
It's not fair.
I have to.
I know how you feel,
but my something freaky is going
on here, Censor, is on high alert.
You've got to trust my powers on this one.
Either you can go see the doctor and
die, or we can turn back now and live.
Which one will it be?
Well, of course I don't want to die.
That's scary.
Oh, that's too bad.
Then, as you wish, I'll have the driver
turn the carriage around for you.
Wait a moment and I shall return.
Stop the carriage!
Listen, Chopper, I'm sorry.
I know what this means to you.
No, I understand.
If I was strong and brave like Luffy,
I could just walk there by myself
instead of sitting here and crying.
How long does he plan
to make us wait here?
Don't know, but I'm too
scared to look outside again.
He's just turning around.
It should only take a sec.
There's nobody here!
Not even the horses!
Not only that, they left us in the
middle of some scary graveyard!
Are you kidding me? But why? What?
No, that can't be right!
Please, someone tell me
you just left it go feed!
Golden! Hey!
Where'd you go?
Leaving us alone at night is one
thing, but come on in a graveyard.
What is it now?
Is that...? No.
This is a dream, right?
Oh
It bit me! Aw, damn it!
It's all over!
I'm gonna turn into a zombie now!
Oh, stop!
Hold on, I'm coming!
No!
Get away from me! Stop it!
Somebody help me!
Let Usopp go!
Eat this!
I'm sorry!
There you dropped this.
Oh, thanks!
Don't let them bite me! Hurry!
Zombie!
I said get off me! Get away!
The exploding star should work.
Zombies hate fire!
No fire! Get back, man! That'll burn you!
I figured it would work,
but I wasn't expecting this.
That's dangerous, you idiot!
Didn't your perish race, you warts?
You little turd!
All right, that got the
zombies out of our way.
Come on, Nami!
Let's get out of here! Right!
At this point,
we might as well make a run for the
mansion since it's closer than the shore.
That sounds like a good idea to me.
That was so scary.
Don't worry. We're fine.
As long as we're able to keep up the pace,
there's no way those things can catch us.
Even if they're strong
and don't get tired,
they shamble along really
slow when they move.
What?
Were they just lazy?
No!
Hey, wait a sec.
They're tired now?
They aren't following us, right?
Man, what is with this island?
Half the stuff here isn't
even supposed to be real.
And by the way,
if I start turning into a zombie and go
after your brains, they'd just kill me!
Where'd that come from?
If you get bit by a zombie, you
turn into one and eat brains.
I read it in a book, so it must be true.
I don't think you're mature
enough for horror novels.
You should stick to children's books.
Well, here we are.
I sure could go for a glass of water.
Haha, I can see him after all. Lucky me.
If he's crazy enough to live here,
I have a feeling he's not going to
be quite as welcoming as you hope.
But fine.
Excuse me?
Is this the mansion of Dr.
Hogback by any chance?